ILGWU International Relations Department publications 5780/062 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 20, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.4 (1990:Sep./Oct.). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.5 (1990:Nov./Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.4 (1991:July/Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.1 (1991:Jan./Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.5 (1990:Nov./Dec.). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.3 (1992:Sep./Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.6 (1991:Nov./Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.5 (1991:Sep./Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.2 (1991:Mar./Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.2 (1990:May/June). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.3 (1990:July/Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.4 (1990:Sep./Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.2 (1992:July/Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.2 (1994:Mar./Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.1 (1992:Jan./June). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.1 (1994:Jan./Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.2 (1993:Mar./May). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.1 (1993:Jan./Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.3 (1991:May/June). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.3 (1993:June/Aug.). Coy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. no.3 (1993:June/Aug.). Item is in English.
- Box: 20, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Facts on Working Women: 20 Facts on Women Workers, Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor: Women's Bureau. no.93-2 (1993:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Facts on Working Women: Earnings Differences Between Women and Men, Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor: Women's Bureau. no.93-5 (1993:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Facts on Working Women: Working Mothers and their Children, Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor: Women's Bureau. no.89-3 (1989:Aug.). Item is in English.
- Box: 21, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Study On The Needs Of Part-Time Female Workers In Hong Kong, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
    By Hong Kong Women Workers Association. Includes poster. Item is in English; Chinese.
- Box: 21, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Sexual Harassment at Work: A Trade Union Guide, Publication (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Trade Unions And Working Women: Manual, Publication (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Box: 21, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Struggle and Development Among Self Employed Women: A Report on the Self Employed, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
    By Office of Urban Development. Item is in English.
- Box: 21, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Workshop on the Status of Women in Trade Unions, Publication (Box 21, Folder 4)
    By International Textile, Garment And Leather Workers Federation. Item is in English.
- Box: 21, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor in the 1990's: Women, Work, and Unions, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
    By Joyce Miller. Item is in English.
- Box: 21, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Charter of the Rights of Working Women, Publication (Box 21, Folder 6)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. Photocopy. Item is in English.
- Box: 21, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Positive Action For Women In Western Europe, Publication (Box 21, Folder 7)
    By ETUI (European Trade Union Institute). Item is in English.
- Box: 21, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Convencion Sobre La Eliminacion De Todas Las Formas De Discriminacion Contra La Mujer, Publication (Box 21, Folder 8)
    By CEDAW (Committee for the Elimination of Discriminaton Against Women). Item is in English.
- Box: 21, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Bargaining for Family Benefits: A Union Member's Guide, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women). Item is in English.
- Box: 21, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Travail: Le Magazine de L'Oit, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
    By Bureau international Du Travail. no.12 (1995:May/June). Item is in French.
- Box: 21, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions And Working Women: Manual, Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Box: 21, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Equality: The Continuing Challenge, Publication (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Box: 21, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Women Workers, Unions and Industrial Sectors in North America, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
    By Susan C. Eaton. Equality for Women in Employment: An Interdepartmental Project. ISP Women/WP-1. Photocopy. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Women Workers, Unions and Industrial Sectors in north America, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
    By Susan C. Eaton. Equality for Women in Employment: An Interdepartmental Project. ISP Women/WP-1. Photocopy. Item is in English.
- Box: 21, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Women Workers: Trands and Issues, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
    By U.S. Department of Labor: Women's Bureau. Item is in English.
- Box: 22, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New Technology and Women's Employment, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU). Item is in English.
- Box: 22, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Las Mueres Trabajadores Del Sector Informal Y La Organizacion Sindical - Cartilla Pedagogica, Publication (Box 22, Folder 2)
    By Departmento de la Mujer Trabajadoras CIOSL/ORIT(La Confederacion de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres/ La Organizacion Regional Interamericana de la Trabajadores). Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 22, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Song Book, Publication (Box 22, Folder 3)
    By International Confederation Of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU). Title repeated in French, German and Spanish. Photocopy. Item is in English; French; German; Spanish.
- Box: 22, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Por Nosotras, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
    By Foro de Capacitacion e Investigacion Para La Mujer Sindicalizada (FOCAI). v.1:no.0 (1991:Apr.). Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 22, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Affirmative Action: 10 Myths, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Canadian Union of Public Employees. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: ICFTU Policy On Work And Family, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Women's Bureau. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor Viewpoint, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Carribean Congress of Labour. v.7:no.1 (1990:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Le Bureau de la main-d'oeuvre feminine, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Labour Canada. Copy 2 of "Women's Bureau". Item is in English; French.
  - Item 5: News: L.E.A.D!, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Women and Philanthropy, Inc. v.17:no.3 (1994:Fall/Winter). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Positive Action: Policies and Guidelines for Trade unions, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: The CLC Women's Bureau, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Canadian Labour Congress. Backside of pamphlet with the same but in french. Item is in English; French.
  - Item 8: We,The Self Employed - voice of the self employed workers, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Self Employed Women's Association (SEWA). November 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Women and Affirmative Action, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Canadian Labour Congress. Back side of pamphlet with same but in french. Item is in English; French.
  - Item 10: Women and Health and Safety, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Canadian Labour Congress. Back side of pamphlet in French. Item is in English; French.
  - Item 11: Women and Unions, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Canadian Labour Congress. Double side pamphlet with the same on the backside but in French. Item is in English; French.
  - Item 12: Women's Bureau, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By Labour Canada. Item is in English; French.
  - Item 13: Working Women, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Box: 22, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Sexual Harassment At Work: A trade Union Guide, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Sexual Harassment At Work: A Trade Union Guide, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Box: 22, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A Mulher Trabalhadora E O Mercosul, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
    By Forca Sindical. Item is in Portuguese.
- Box: 22, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Report on Young Women Works in Korea, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
    By Fred J. Krampert. Photocopy. Item is in Portuguese.
- Box: 22, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Les Cahiers des Femmes Syndicalistes; FO: La Force En Liberte, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
    By Confederation Generale du Travail Force Ouvriere. n.2 (1990:Dec.). Item is in French.
- Box: 22, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Igualdad Algo Mas Que Palabras: Derechos De La Mujer, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
    By CIPAF: Campana Igualdad algo mas que palabras. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 22, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Moving Borders: Women and the trade unions in the Netherlands, Publication (Box 22, Folder 11)
    By Netherlands Trade Union Confederation FNV. Cover in English, French, German, and Spanish. Text English only. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 22, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Women in the National Union, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
    By National Union of Provincial Government Employees. Item is in English; French.
- Box: 22, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Equal Opportunities: Harassment Awareness Kit, Publication (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Box: 22, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: 10 Pay Equity Myths, Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Box: 22, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Equality: The Continuing Challenge-Strategies for Success: Working Paper I: The Empowerment of Women: Their Full Participation in Society, Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. 5th World Women's Conference, Ottawa, Canada, 21-25 April 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Equality: The Continuing Challenge-Strategies for Success:Working Paper II: Claiming Our Rightful Place and Worth: Recognition of Women's Economic Status, Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Equality: The Continuing Challenge-Strategies for Success:Working Paper III: A Women's place is Leading Her Union: Full Integration of Women into Trade Unions, Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: ICFTU-APRO: Asia Pacific Women's Symposium on "Equality: Continuing Challenge, Future Stratgies", Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. New Delhi, 7-10 February 1990. Item is in English.
- Box: 22, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Women's Commision Newsletter, Publication (Box 22, Folder 16)
    By Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children. no.5 (1993:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Women's Commission News, Publication (Box 22, Folder 16)
    By Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children. no.1 (1991:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Women's Commission Newsletter, Publication (Box 22, Folder 16)
    By Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children. no.2 (1991:June). Item is in English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: ILO Poster, Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    By ILO (International Labor Organization). Item is in English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Guia De Los Derechos De Los Trabajadores, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By Rafael Alburquerque. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 23, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Annual Report: 1988, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By IRC (International Rescue Committee). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Summary of Activities 1992, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Conferencia Internacional: Integracion Desarrollo y Democracia, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By CIOSL/ORIT. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: Guestworker Programs: Lessons from Europe, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By US Department of Labor. Bureau of International Labor Affairs, Monograph no.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Proclaiming Migrants Rights, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By World Council of Churches. Churches' Committee for Migrants in Europe, Briefing Papers no.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Refugees, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By UNHCR (United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees). no.89 (1992:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Problems of Young Migrant Workers, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By ICFTU. Report of a study session organised from 11 to 15 June, 1973 in Fulda, Germany. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: To Be An Immigrant In New York City In The Nineteen-Eighties, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By Sandra Golstein. Master's Thesis. Item is in English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Convention General De Protection Sociale De La Siderurgie Du 24 Juillet 1984, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    By GESIM (Groupement des Entreprises Siderurgiques et Metallurgiques). Item is in English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By ICFTU. Item is in English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Human Rights: The International Bill of Human Rights, Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Box: 23, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Corporate Examiner, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    By Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility. v.22:no.3 (1993). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Corporate Examiner, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    By Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility. v.22:no.8/9 (1993). Item is in English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Free Trade Union News, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
    By AFL-CIO. v.37:no.10 (1982:Oct.). Item is in English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Derechos Humanos y Sindicales, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    By CIOSL/ORIT. no.2 (1993:Apr./Nov.). Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 23, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: El Comercio Y Los Derechos De Los Trabajadores: La Proxima Frontera De La Democracia, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By Instituto Americano para el Desarrollo del Sindicalismo Libre. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 23, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The North.South Debate: Technology, Basic Human needs and the New International Economic Order, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
    By Johan Galtung. World Order Models Project Working Paper no.12. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Struggle for a Just World Order; An Agenda of Inquiry of Praxis for the 1980's, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
    By Saul H. Mendolovitz. World Order Models Project Working Paper no.20. Item is in English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Taller Sobre "Democracia Liberizacion Del Comercio Y Derechos Laborales", Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    By Federacion Internacional De Trabajadores Del Textil, Vestido, Cuero, Calzado. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 23, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Hotline Justice and Peace Newsletter: A Forgotten Word in Human Rights, Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
    By Commission for Justice and Peace. no.80 (1994:Aug./Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Hotline Newsletter: Caretaker Government, Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
    By Commission for Justice and Peace. no.89 (1996:Feb./Mar.). Item is in English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Field Guide to Labor Rights, Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
    By Jim Sugarman. Item is in English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: What Price Freedom?: A Profile of the Indonesian Legain Aid Foundation, Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
    By Yayasan Lembaga Bantuan Hukum Indonesia. Item is in English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Informal Sector and Worker Rights, Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
    By US Department of Labor. Foreign Labor Trends no.93-9. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Worker Rights in Export Processing Zones, Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
    By US Department of Labor. Foreign Labor Trends no.90-32. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Worker Rights in US Policy, Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
    By US Department of Labor. Foreign Labor Trends no.91-54. Item is in English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Worker Rights News, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By International Labor Rights Fund. no.5 (1993:Spring). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Worker Rights News, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By International Labor Rights Fund. no.6 (1993:Summer). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Worker Rights News, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By International Labor Rights Fund. no.7 (1993:Fall). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Worker Rights News, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By International Labor Rights Fund. no.8 (1994:Winter). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Worker Rights News, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By International Labor Rights Fund. no.9 (1994:Spring). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Worker Rights News, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By International Labor Rights Fund. no.12 (1995:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Worker Rights News, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By International Labor Rights Fund. no.11 (1994/1995:Fall/Winter). Item is in English.
- Box: 23, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: A Plea to Support the WDL: HeyWhat is the WDL?, Publication (Box 23, Folder 18)
    By Workers Defense League, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: AIFLD Outlook, Publication (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Trade and Workers' Rights: Time For A Link, Publication (Box 23, Folder 18)
    By International Metalworker's Federation. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Worker Rights and Trade: Democracy's Next Frontier, Publication (Box 23, Folder 18)
    By David Jessup. Item is in English.
- Box: 24, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: FNV-News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By FNV. no.2 (1986:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: FNV-News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By FNV. no.6 (1990:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: FNV-News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By FNV. no.4 (1992:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: FNV-News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By FNV. no.3 (1992:Sept.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: FNV-News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By FNV. no.8 (1993:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: FNV-News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By FNV. no.7 (1993:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: FNV-News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By FNV. no.6 (1993:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: FNV-News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By FNV. no.5 (1993:Ap.). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: FNV-News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By FNV. no.11 (1994:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: FNV-News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By FNV. no.9 (1994:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: FNV-News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By FNV. no.13 (1995:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: FNV-News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By FNV. no.12 (1995:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: FNV-News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    By FNV. Item is in English.
- Box: 24, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report for April, 1985, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By Comision Permanente de Derechos Humanos de Nicaragua (CPDH). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report for August, 1985, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Report for February 1986, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Report for February, 1985, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Report for January 1986, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Report for July 1985, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Report for June, 1985, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Report for March, 1985, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Report for May 1986, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By Comision Permanente de Derechos Humanos de Nicaragua (CPDH). May. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Report for May, 1985, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Report for October 1985, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Report for September 1985, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Testimony of Sofonias Cisneros Leiva, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    By Comision Permanente de Derechos Humanos de Nicaragua (CPDH). May, 1985. Item is in English.